Abraham Ribicoff Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Senate Records, 1963-1980 (Box 22-616)
  - Legislative file (Box 390)
    - Appropriations Committee
      - Public Works, 1968, Jan.-1980, June, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany (Box 397)
        - 1967, May-1973, Oct., (7 folders)
        - 1973, Feb.-1977, Dec., (8 folders) (Box 398)
        - 1978, Jan.-1980, Oct., (2 folders) (Box 399)
      - Treasury Department and Post Office Department, 1973, Mar.-1974, Oct.
      - Supersonic transport, 1969, Jan.-1971, Mar., (6 folders)
    - Armed Services Committee (Box 400)
    - Budget Committee
      - General, 1975, Jan.-1980, June, (5 folders)
      - Economic Policy, 1975, Dec.-1976, Dec., (3 folders) (Box 401)
      - Income taxes, 1976, Jan.-Dec.
      - General taxation
        - 1975, Dec.-1976, Mar., (5 folders)
        - 1976 (Box 402)
          - Apr.-June, (7 folders)
          - June-July, (6 folders) (Box 403)
          - July-Sept., (7 folders) (Box 404)
          - Sept.-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 405)
      - Trade, 1976
        - Jan.-Apr., (2 folders)
        - May-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 406)
      - Social Security, Medicare, 1976
        - Jan.-June, (4 folders)
        - Aug.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 407)
      - Inflation, 1976, Jan.-Oct.
      - Health and Medicaid, 1980, Jan.-Nov.
      - Revenue Sharing, 1979, Oct.-1980, Mar.
    - Finance Committee
      - Trade and tariffs
        - 1969, Mar.-1964, Oct., (3 folders)
        - 1964, Sept.-1966, June, (7 folders) (Box 408)
        - 1965, Jan.-1966, Nov., (9 folders) (Box 409)
        - 1967, Mar.-1971, Sept., (7 folders) (Box 410)
        - 1969, June-1976, Apr., (7 folders) (Box 411)
        - 1970, Jan.-1971, Dec., (7 folders) (Box 412)
        - 1972, Jan.-1973, Sept., (8 folders) (Box 413)
        - 1973, Oct.-1974, Oct., (6 folders) (Box 414)
        - 1974, Nov.-1975, Dec., (7 folders) (Box 415)
        - 1977, (9 folders) (Box 416)
        - 1978 (Box 417)
          - Jan.-Apr., (8 folders)
          - Apr.-Aug., (8 folders) (Box 418)
        - 1978-1980, Sept., (4 folders) (Box 419)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 420)
      - Welfare reform, 1979, Jan.-1980, Nov., (2 folders) (Box 421)
      - Miscellany, 1979, Nov.-1980, Oct., (2 folders)
    - Foreign Relations Committee
      - Arms control/sales, 1975, Jan.-1980, Sept., (3 folders)
      - Middle East (Box 422)
        - 1967, Dec.-1970, June, (9 folders)
        - 1970, July-1977, May, (7 folders) (Box 423)
        - 1977, June-1978, Mar., (8 folders) (Box 424)
        - 1978, Mar.-Aug., (9 folders) (Box 425)
        - 1978, Aug.-1980, Aug., (4 folders) (Box 426)
      - Foreign aid, 1979, July-Nov.
      - Soviet Union/détente, 1979, Jan.-1980, July, (2 folders) (Box 427)
      - Romania, 1976, June-Nov.
    - Governmental Affairs Committee
      - Postal matters
        - 1967, Jan.-1968, Aug.
        - 1968, Dec.-1970, May, (8 folders) (Box 428)
        - 1970, May-1976, Oct., (9 folders) (Box 429)
        - 1976, Dec.-1977, (3 folders) (Box 430)
      - Civil Service
        - 1970, Feb.-1977, (6 folders)
        - 1975-1979, (7 folders) (Box 431)
      - Census, 1968, May-1970, Apr., (6 folders) (Box 432)
      - Investigations
        - 1964, Jan.-1970, Apr., (6 folders)
        - 1970, May-1971, May, (6 folders) (Box 433)
        - 1971 (Box 434)
        - 1971, June-1974, July, (6 folders) (Box 435)
      - National security and international operations, 1969-1976 (Box 436)
      - Intergovernmental relations, 1971-1976, (2 folders)
      - Executive reorganization, 1968-1976, (5 folders)
      - Miscellany (noncommittee)
        - Inflation and high cost of medicare, 1969-1970, (2 folders)
        - National priorities
          - 1969
          - 1969 (Box 437)
        - Student unrest and violence, 1969-1971, (4 folders)
        - Miscellaneous
          - 1969, Mar.-1972, Apr., (4 folders)
          - 1972, May-1977, Aug., (6 folders) (Box 438)
          - 1977, Sept.-1978, Dec., (7 folders) (Box 439)
          - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 440)
          - 1980 (Box 441)
        - Vietnam military club investigations
          - 1969-1971, (3 folders)
          - 1972 (Box 442)
        - Corvair investigations, 1970-1974, (2 folders)
        - Public relations in federal government, 1976-1979, (3 folders)
    - Energy and Natural Resource Committee (Box 443)
      - Mining, material, and fuels
        - 1970, Nov.-1976, Oct., (8 folders)
        - 1976, Nov.-1977, Apr., (8 folders) (Box 444)
        - 1977, May-Oct., (7 folders) (Box 445)
        - 1977, Nov.-1978, Dec., (5 folders) (Box 446)
        - 1978, Dec.-1980, Nov., (2 folders) (Box 447)
      - Wildlife protection
        - 1969, Nov.-1971, Sept., (3 folders)
        - 1975, Dec.-1977, Feb., (9 folders) (Box 448)
        - 1977, Mar.-Sept., (9 folders) (Box 449)
        - 1977, Oct.-1978, May, (9 folders) (Box 450)
        - 1978, June-1980, Nov., (6 folders) (Box 451)
      - Energy (Box 452)
        - 1977
          - Jan.-Apr., (8 folders)
          - May-Aug., (8 folders) (Box 453)
          - Sept.-Nov., (8 folders) (Box 454)
        - 1977, Nov.-1978, July, (7 folders) (Box 455)
        - 1978, Aug.-1980, Nov., (3 folders) (Box 456)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 457)
      - Public lands, 1971, July-1976, Dec., (6 folders) (Box 458)
      - Miscellany
        - 1964, Oct.-1970, July, (3 folders)
        - 1970, Sept.-1971, Mar., (8 folders) (Box 459)
        - 1971, Apr.-1978, Dec., (6 folders) (Box 460)
        - 1979, Apr.-1980, Nov., (2 folders) (Box 461)
    - Labor and Human Resources Committee
      - Health, 1977, Jan.-1978, July, (2 folders)
      - Education, 1970, Aug.-Dec., (2 folders)
      - Employment, poverty, migratory, 1977, Jan.-1979, Mar., (4 folders) (Box 462)
      - Pollution
        - 1969, June-1970, Apr., (2 folders)
        - 1970, May-1977, Aug., (6 folders) (Box 463)
        - 1979, Feb.-Nov. (Box 464)
      - Aging, 1976, Aug.-1979, April
    - Joint Economic Committee
      - 1966, May-1977, Dec., (6 folders)
      - 1978, Jan.-1979, Dec., (5 folders) (Box 465)
      - 1980, Jan.-Oct. (Box 466)
    - Environment and Public Works Committee
      - Flood control, 1974, July-1980, June
      - Rivers and harbors, 1975, Apr.-1980, Sept., (4 folders)
      - Public roads and highways
        - 1972, Sept.-1974, Nov.
        - 1975, Jan.-1979, Apr., (2 folders) (Box 467)
      - Public buildings and grounds, 1975, Jan.-1978, Dec., (5 folders)
      - Miscellany
        - 1972, Oct.-1976, Mar., (4 folders)
        - 1976, Apr.-1977, July, (8 folders) (Box 468)
        - 1977, Aug.-1980, Nov., (3 folders) (Box 469)
    - Miscellany
      - 1969, Sept.-1970, Mar., (3 folders)
      - 1970, Apr.-Aug., (7 folders) (Box 470)
      - 1970, Sept.-1976, May, (8 folders) (Box 471)
      - 1976, June-Dec., (7 folders) (Box 472)
      - 1977, Jan.-1980, Sept., (9 folders) (Box 473)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 474)
    - Bill file
      - 88th Congress, 1963-1964
        - Bills
          - S.4-S.6, (2 folders)
          - S.360-S.432, (3 folders) (Box 475)
          - S.432-S.470, (4 folders) (Box 476)
          - S.486-S.1605, (12 folders) (Box 477)
          - S.1666-S.1988, (10 folders) (Box 478)
          - S.2031-S.2642, (11 folders) (Box 479)
        - Resolutions
          - S.R.30-S.R.55, (2 folders)
          - S.R. (Box 480)
        - Joint resolutions, 17-176, (7 folders)
        - Concurrent resolution 2 (Box 481)
        - Amendments
          - 281-1054, (7 folders)
          - 1174-11376, (10 folders) (Box 482)
      - 89th Congress, 1965-1966 (Box 483)
        - Bills
          - S.3-S.12, (4 folders)
          - S.12-S.306, (10 folders) (Box 484)
          - S.309-S.325, (5 folders) (Box 485)
          - S.325-S.370, (2 folders) (Box 486)
          - S.400-S.944, (18 folders) (Box 487)
          - S.948-S.1564, (13 folders) (Box 488)
          - S.1564-S.2152, (14 folders) (Box 489)
          - S.2218-S.2302, (8 folders) (Box 490)
          - S.2318-S.3171, (15 folders) (Box 491)
          - S.3182-S.868, (11 folders) (Box 492)
          - Resolutions, S.R.121-302, (11 folders) (Box 493)
          - Concurrent resolutions
            - 4-17, (3 folders)
            - 17, (3 folders) (Box 494)
            - 43-83, (6 folders) (Box 495)
          - Amendments (Box 496)
            - 143-617, (13 folders)
            - 637-8147, (6 folders) (Box 497)
      - 90th Congress, 1967-1968 (Box 498)
        - Bills
          - S.9-S.514, (11 folders)
          - S.538-S.804, (16 folders) (Box 499)
          - S.835, (7 folders) (Box 500)
          - S.835-S.950, (4 folders) (Box 501)
          - S.1026, (6 folders) (Box 502)
          - S.1026-S1150, (5 folders) (Box 503)
          - S.1240-S.1585, (13 folders) (Box 504)
          - S.1593-S.1976, (11 folders) (Box 505)
          - S.1985-S.2270, (14 folders) (Box 506)
          - S.2293-S.2481, (6 folders) (Box 507)
          - S.2481-S.2616, (9 folders) (Box 508)
          - S.2618-S.2907, (8 folders) (Box 509)
          - S.2907-S.3158, (6 folders) (Box 510)
          - S.3181-S.3279, (6 folders) (Box 511)
          - S.3287-S.3643, (5 folders) (Box 512)
          - Resolutions
            - S.R.8-S.R.281, (9 folders)
            - S.R.281-S.R.383, (4 folders) (Box 513)
          - Joint resolutions, 4-175, (8 folders)
          - Concurrent resolutions, 24-53, (4 folders)
        - Amendments
          - 163-295, (4 folders)
          - 299-2365, (16 folders) (Box 514)
      - 91st Congress, 1969-1970
        - Bills
          - S.1-S.303, (12 folders) (Box 515)
          - S.472-S.860, (11 folders) (Box 516)
          - S.942-S.1584, (11 folders) (Box 517)
          - S.1585-S.1846, (7 folders) (Box 518)
          - S.1959-S.2673, (18 folders) (Box 519)
          - S.2701-S.2993, (5 folders) (Box 520)
          - S.2968-S.4464, (4 folders) (Box 521)
          - Joint resolutions, 8-110, (2 folders)
          - Miscellany, (2 folders); (5 folders) (Box 522)
      - 92nd Congress, 1971-1972 (Box 523)
        - Bills
          - S.186-S.317, (7 folders)
          - S.376 (Box 524)
          - S.376, (2 folders) (Box 525)
          - S.376-S.869, (6 folders) (Box 526)
          - S.880-S.1282, (10 folders) (Box 527)
          - S. 1282-S.1283, (2 folders) (Box 528)
          - S.1282-S.1460, (9 folders) (Box 529)
          - S.1485-S.1828, (7 folders) (Box 530)
          - S.1527-S.2460, (6 folders) (Box 531)
          - S.2515-S.2994, (13 folders) (Box 532)
          - S.3037-S.3409, (9 folders) (Box 533)
          - S.3432-S.3632, (5 folders) (Box 534)
          - S.3700-S.3739, (3 folders) (Box 535)
          - S.3750-S.4070, (10 folders) (Box 536)
        - Resolutions
          - S.R.45-S.R.177, (2 folders)
          - S.R.180-S.R.367, (5 folders) (Box 537)
        - Joint resolutions, 1-15, (4 folders)
        - Joint resolutions, 206-244, (2 folders) (Box 538)
        - Concurrent resolutions, 21-55, (6 folders)
        - Amendments
          - 46-159, (6 folders)
          - 318-559, (3 folders) (Box 539)
          - 559 (Box 540)
          - 628-912, (9 folders) (Box 541)
          - 958-1307, (7 folders) (Box 542)
          - 1462-1669, (3 folders) (Box 543)
          - Correspondence regarding welfare amendments, (1 folder); (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box 544, Box 545)
      - 93rd Congress, 1973-1974 (Box 546)
        - Bills
          - S.48-S.1030, (22 folders)
          - S.1125-S.2513, (12 folders) (Box 547)
          - S.2513-S.3130, (10 folders) (Box 548)
          - S.3154-S.4225, (12 folders) (Box 549)
        - Resolutions
          - S.R.67-S.R.189, (6 folders)
          - S.R.189-S.R.397, (8 folders) (Box 550)
        - Joint resolutions, 2-12, (9 folders)
        - Concurrent resolutions, 66-110, (3 folders) (Box 551)
        - Amendments
          - 6-43, (3 folders)
          - 32-542, (4 folders) (Box 552)
          - 542-2064, (17 folders) (Box 553)
        - Miscellany
      - 94th. Congress, 1975-1976 (Box 554)
        - Bills
          - S.5-S.200, (9 folders)
          - S.388-S.850, (22 folders) (Box 555)
          - S.961-S.1793, (16 folders) (Box 556)
          - S.1487-S.2541, (19 folders) (Box 557)
          - S.2596-S.3425, (14 folders) (Box 558)
        - Resolutions
          - S.R.4-S.R.400, (6 folders)
          - S.R.413 (Box 559)
        - Joint resolutions, 1-66, (5 folders)
        - Concurrent resolutions, 2-86, (5 folders)
        - Amendments, 360-1423, (4 folders)
      - 95th Congress, 1977-1978
        - Bills
          - S.2-S.298, (10 folders)
          - S.311 (Box 560)
          - S.311-S.995, (18 folders) (Box 561)
          - S.1064-S.1899, (18 folders) (Box 562)
          - S.1968-S.2066, (3 folders) (Box 563)
          - S.2115-S.2503, (12 folders) (Box 564)
          - S.2511-S.3542, (7 folders) (Box 565)
          - Resolutions, S.R.127-S.R.541, (6 folders)
          - Joint resolutions, 1-210, (11 folders)
          - Concurrent resolutions, 7
          - Amendments, 21-1033, (3 folders)
      - 96th Congress, 1979-1980 (Box 566)
        - Bills
          - S.2-S.345, (18 folders)
          - S.350-S.1376, (31 folders) (Box 567)
          - AAR's bills and co-sponsors (Box 568)
          - Declined to sponsor, 1980, (5 folders)
          - Joint letters, (2 folders)
          - Miscellaneous correspondence
    - Legislative Assistance File (Box 569)
      - Connecticut Issues, 1969-1980
        - Appalachian trail, (2 folders)
        - Housatonic Valley Area
        - Long Island Sound, (5 folders)
        - Miscellany
        - Rivers, (12 folders) (Box 570)
      - Miscellaneous issues (Box 571)
        - Agriculture
        - Business speech background material
        - Health insurance
        - Judgeships, (2 folders)
        - National Institutes of Health
        - Nazis, alleged and hunters
        - Operation recognition
        - Productivity conference, (3 folders)
        - Soviet Jewry, (10 folders) (Box 572)
        - Soviet Union, general, (2 folders)
        - Trade, (2 folders)
        - Totalization agreements (Box 573)
        - Work sharing
        - Youth camp safety, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany
        - Memoranda, (5 folders)
    - Legislative assistants' file (Box 574)
      - Chronological file, Stuart Brahs, 1979, Jan.-Aug., (8 folders)
      - Koskinen, John Andrew (Box 575)
        - Education, segregation
          - 1970-1972, (12 folders)
          - 1971-1972, (6 folders) (Box 576)
        - Immigration, private bills
        - Jeeps
        - Northeast utilities, 1973-1974
      - Campbell, Malcolm (Box 577)
        - “A-D” miscellaneous, (20 folders)
        - Electric boat, 1977-1978, (6 folders) (Box 578)
        - “H-N” miscellaneous, (21 folders) (Box 579)
        - “N-T” miscellaneous, (20 folders) (Box 580)
        - “T-Z” miscellaneous, (13 folders) (Box 581)
      - House, Arthur (Box 582)
        - Foreign travel
          - Moscow, Soviet Union trip, 1975
          - Soviet Union parliamentary conference, June 25-1975, July 6
          - Middle East trip, 1976, Nov., (2 folders)
          - Conference on International Economic Cooperation, 1977, (2 folders)
          - Soviet Union parliamentarians' conference, 1878, Jan., (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 583)
        - Foreign affairs miscellany
          - 1977, (6 folders)
          - 1977, Sept.-1978, Sept., (19 folders) (Box 584)
          - 1978, Oct.-1979, Sept., (15 folders) (Box 585)
          - 1979, Oct.-1980, Apr., (12 folders) (Box 586)
      - Schaefer, David (Box 587)
        - Danbury, Conn., prison fire
        - Special Committee on Official Conduct (Nelson) S.R.110, 1977, (13 folders); (7 folders) (Box 588)
        - Select Committee on Ethics, S.555
          - 1977-1979
          - 1977-1979, (10 folders) (Box 589)
          - 1978, (10 folders); (9 folders) (Box 590, Box 591)
          - 1978-1979, (8 folders) (Box 592)
          - 1978-1979, (7 folders) (Box 593)
        - Bert Lance Hearings
          - 1977, (8 folders); (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box 594, Box 595)
        - Soviet Union trip, 1978, (9 folders)
        - Finance Committee, 1976-1979, (7 folders) (Box 596)
        - Judiciary Committee, 1976-1979, (5 folders)
      - Seigel, John (Box 597)
        - Agriculture, 1979-1980, (2 folders)
        - Appropriations, 1979, (5 folders)
        - Budget
          - 1979-1981, (7 folders)
          - 1981, (3 folders) (Box 598)
        - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1979-1980
        - Child Welfare Bill, H.R.3434, 1979, (6 folders)
        - Chrysler bailout
        - Crop insurance, 1979 (Box 599)
        - Davis-Bacon Act
        - Disability, 1979-1980, (10 folders)
        - Education
          - 1978-1979, (6 folders)
          - 1979, (11 folders) (Box 600)
        - Unemployment bill, 1979-1980 (Box 601)
        - Welfare reform, 1976-1980, (12 folders)
        - Miscellany
        - Joint Economic Committee, 1980 (Box 602)
        - Federal Trade Commission, 1980
        - Finance Committee, 1980
        - Targeted Fiscal Assistance, 1979
        - Food stamps, 1979
        - Rights of institutionalized
        - Special Milk Program
        - School lunch
        - Small business
        - Social Security funding
        - Council on Wage and Price Stability
        - Unemployment compensation
        - Taxes, (2 folders)
      - D'Amato, C. Richard (Box 603)
        - Windfall Profits Tax
          - 1979-1980, (6 folders)
      - Luks, Harold P. (Box 604)
        - Amtrak authorization
        - Ammonia
        - Brass industry
        - Ball bearings
        - Bolts, nuts, and screws
        - Boycott, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 605)
        - Color television (Box 606)
        - Connecticut banking
        - Connecticut transportation
        - Credit unions
        - Czech gold
        - Eurodollar market
        - Exporting trade companies
        - Footwear
        - Hungarian most favored nation
        - Intelligence charter (Box 607)
        - Interstate 84
        - Interstate 291
        - Memoranda to AAR
          - 1978-1980, (4 folders)
        - Norwalk, Conn. (Box 608)
        - North American economic cooperation
        - Ocean policy and fisheries
        - Olympics, 1976
        - Overseas Private Investment Corp.
        - Poughkeepsie bridge
        - Pfizer v. India (Box 609)
        - Refugee-immigration cases
        - Regulation Q, small savers
        - Rhodesia
        - Romanian most favored nation, 1980, (4 folders)
        - Soviet trip
        - Soviet Jewry (Box 610)
        - Steel
        - Tax exempt bonds and bills, (2 folders)
        - Taxation forces return from abroad (Box 611)
        - Taxation overseas
        - Trade cases
        - Transportation
        - Trucking deregulation (Box 612)
        - United Nations, (2 folders)
        - United Technologies
        - Watches
        - Wine gallon/proof gallon
        - Miscellany (Box 613)
          - Morning memoranda, 1974-1977, (6 folders)
        - Parsons, Judy (Box 614)
          - Child health care assessment program, (5 folders); (6 folders); (9 folders) (Box 615, Box 616)
- Political Papers, 1962-1980 (Box 617-644)
  Correspondence, subject files, and campaign files.
  - Correspondence (Box 617)
    - Personal
      - 1962-1964, (6 folders)
      - 1965-1977, (5 folders) (Box 618)
    - General
      - 1962, (7 folders); (6 folders) (Box 619)
    - Political, 1962, (2 folders) (Box 620)
    - Reading file, 1967-1968, (2 folders)
  - Subject file
    - Appreciation letters
    - Birchwood Country Club
    - Condolences, 1967-1968, (2 folders)
    - Congratulations, 1962, 1967-1968, (3 folders)
    - Congratulations (Box 621)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1965
    - Democratic newsletter, 1964-1968, (4 folders)
    - Grants
      - 1966-1968, (2 folders)
    - Greetings, 1962, (2 folders)
    - Invitations regretted, 1962, Dec.
    - Miscellany
    - Organization memberships
    - Ribicoff, Lois
    - Retirement letters, 1979, Sept.-1980, Dec.
    - Schedules, 1965, 1967, (3 folders) (Box 622)
    - Senatorial districts, 1963-1967, (7 folders)
    - Tumblebrook Country Club
    - White House
  - Campaign file
    - 1950
      - House of Representatives
      - Speeches, (8 folders)
    - 1952, U.S. Senate (Box 623)
    - 1954, gubernatorial, (6 folders)
    - 1958
      - Gubernatorial, (7 folders)
      - Contributions, (4 folders) (Box 624)
    - 1960, presidential (Box 625)
    - 1962
      - United States Senate
        - Calendar
        - Committee, (5 folders)
        - Contributions, (3 folders)
      - Contributions, (4 folders) (Box 626)
      - Correspondence
      - Delegates
      - Democratic meetings
      - Form letters
      - Honorary degrees
      - Issues, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 627)
      - Labor, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany
      - New London, Conn., supper
      - Newsletter
      - Offers of assistance, (2 folders)
      - Parcel post requests
      - Political
      - Press party
      - Radio, television, and press
      - Randolph-Wolf (Box 628)
      - Republicans, Independents, and Senior Citizens for Ribicoff
      - Requests for photographs
      - Ribicoff-Kowalski
      - Telegrams
      - Telethon, (4 folders)
      - Towns, Connecticut
        - “A” miscellaneous-Branford
        - Bridgeport-New Britain, (8 folders) (Box 629)
        - New Canaan-Woodbury (Box 630)
      - Platform
      - Speeches, (4 folders) (Box 631)
      - Press releases, (2 folders)
      - Invitations accepted, (6 folders) (Box 632)
    - 1963-1964, Connecticut mailings, (2 folders) (Box 633)
    - 1968
      - Billboards
      - Committee correspondence
      - Contributors' acknowledgments
      - Delegates
      - Friends of Ribicoff, (1 folder) (Box 634)
      - Literature
      - Miscellany, (4 folders)
      - News releases
      - Source book, (2 folders)
    - 1974 (Box 635)
      - Advertisements
      - Bank statements
      - Budget
      - Candidates, (7 folders)
      - Committee
      - Contributions, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 636)
      - Correspondence, (5 folders)
      - Delegates
      - Democratic women's clubs
      - Deposit slips
      - Endorsements, (4 folders)
      - Fairfield, Conn., office (Box 637)
      - Federal filing forms
      - Form letters
      - Internal Revenue Service
      - Fund raining
      - Guggenheim Productions (Box 638)
      - Invitations, (6 folders)
      - Issues, (2 folders)
      - Ledger sheets, (2 folders)
      - Leonhardt, Cliff, (2 folders) (Box 639)
      - Mailing list, (2 folders)
      - Media
      - Materials sent out
      - Messages to read
      - Miscellany, (1 folder); (8 folders); (2 folders) (Box 640, Box 641)
      - Office equipment
      - Office memoranda
      - Opponents
      - Payroll
      - Pending
      - People for Ribicoff
      - Phone bills
      - Postage receipts
      - Post office permit
      - Press, (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box 642)
      - Radio advertisements
      - Reading file
      - Receipts, (2 folders)
      - Refunds
      - Reports, (2 folders)
      - Requests for buttons
      - Schedules, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 643)
      - Speeches, (2 folders)
      - Staff lists, (2 folders)
      - State central committee, (2 folders)
      - Statistics
      - Stratford letter and mailing list, (3 folders)
      - Suisman mailing
      - Telephone
      - Thank-you letters
      - Town chairman, (2 folders)
      - Tumblebrook Country Club (Box 644)
      - TV advertisements
      - Women's club
      - Workers
      - Zip codes
- Miscellany, 1927-1981 (Box 644-676)
  Voting records, biographical information, article and book file, reports, scrapbooks and memorabilia.
  - Voting record (Box 644)
    - House of Representatives, 1949-1952
    - Roll call votes, 1963
    - Record
      - 1963-1973, (7 folders)